This is getting hard
to not take personally.
(Penny:)- Come on. Don't make this about you.
- I'm not. It's about you.
Yeah, whatever.
I told you Valentine's Day sucks.
- This one does, and you're the reason why.
- What?
(Bernadette:)Compared to them,
I'm feeling pretty good about us.
(Howard:)Me too. How about we blow off dessert,
go home early? I'll do that laundry.
(Alex:)Thank you.
- I love you.
- Love you too.
- So where'd you hide it?
- Where you'd never look.
(Howard:)Damn it, it's in the washing machine.
- Hello.
- Happy Valentine's Day.
- Okay.
(Sheldon:)- Shall we go to dinner?
- Hang on.
(Amy:)As you know,
I had planned a traditional evening...
(Amy:)...of romance and gifts.
(Sheldon:)Yes, and as you know,
I planned to pretend to enjoy it.